I've been in Colorado on a Saturday night, just how wish she was at home.
我在科罗拉多的一个星期六夜晚，只希望她能在家。
She's mad because the baby just ain't treating her right, so afraid of being alone.
她很生气，因为孩子对她不好，她害怕一个人孤独。
Said she's heard some stories, even running around.
她说她听过一些故事，甚至有人到处跑。
Said somehow she knows it's all true.
她说不知怎么的，她知道这都是真的。
She said a breaking heart can make a terrible sound.
她说，一颗破碎的心会发出可怕的声音。
Said she just don't know what to do.
她说她不知道该怎么办。
Think about it that time, you can't get much worse.
想想那个时候，情况不会更糟了。
Think about a hard life, take it to the wall.
想想艰难的生活，撞向墙壁。
This won't be the last time, cause you're ain't the first.
这不会是最后一次，因为你不是第一个。
The bigger they are, the harder they fall.
他们越大，摔得越惨。
You might say she's calm between a rock and a hard place.
你可以说她被夹在夹缝中。
You might think she just can't win.
也许你会觉得她永远无法胜利。
Sound just can't recover from a slap in her face.
声音似乎无法从她脸上的一记耳光中恢复过来。
Some could just ride up, start all over again.
有些人可能重新站起来，重新开始。
Think about it that time, you can't get much worse.
想想那个时候，情况不会更糟了。
Think about a hard life, take it to the wall.
想想艰难的生活，撞向墙壁。
This won't be the last time, cause you're ain't the first.
这不会是最后一次，因为你不是第一个。
The bigger they are, the harder they fall.
他们越大，摔得越惨。
Think about it that time, you can't get much worse.
想想那个时候，情况不会更糟了。
Think about a hard life, take it to the wall.
想想艰难的生活，撞向墙壁。
This won't be the last time, cause you're ain't the first.
这不会是最后一次，因为你不是第一个。
The bigger they are, the harder they fall.
他们越大，摔得越惨。
Think about it that time, you can't get much worse.
想想那个时候，情况不会更糟了。
Think about a hard life, take it to the wall.
想想艰难的生活，撞向墙壁。
This won't be the last time it's your ring the first.
这不会是最后一次，你并非第一个。
The bigger they are, the harder they fall.
他们越大，摔得越惨。
Aspen Colorado on a Saturday night.
在科罗拉多州的阿斯彭，一个星期六的夜晚。
Just say when she was at home.
就在她在家的时候。
She's nice because maybe ain't treating her right.
她生气了，因为也许对她不好，
But so afraid of being alone.
但是很害怕一个人孤独。
She's so afraid of being alone.
她很害怕一个人孤独。
Nobody wants to be alone no more.
没有人想再孤独下去了。
I don't want to sleep alone no more.
我不想再一个人睡了。
Thank you for watching!
谢谢观看！